[('The Grammy Awards ceremony, hosted by the National Academy of Recording Arts and Sciences, showcased exceptional musical talent from around the world.', {'entities': [(4, 17, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (38, 89, 'ORG')]}), ("The Vienna Philharmonic Orchestra, known for its rich history and exquisite performances, captivated audiences with their rendition of Beethoven's Symphony No.", {'entities': [(0, 33, 'ORG'), (135, 144, 'PERSON')]}), ('9.', {'entities': [(0, 1, 'CARDINAL')]}), ('The Rolling Stones, a legendary rock band formed in London, England, embarked on a world tour to celebrate their 50th anniversary.', {'entities': [(0, 18, 'ORG'), (52, 58, 'GPE'), (60, 67, 'GPE'), (113, 117, 'ORDINAL')]}), ('The Metropolitan Opera, located in New York City, is renowned for its grand opera productions and attracts opera enthusiasts from all over the globe.', {'entities': [(0, 22, 'ORG'), (35, 48, 'GPE')]}), ("The National Symphony Orchestra, based in Washington, D.C., collaborated with the renowned pianist Lang Lang to deliver an unforgettable rendition of Rachmaninoff's Piano Concerto No.", {'entities': [(0, 31, 'ORG'), (42, 52, 'GPE'), (54, 58, 'GPE'), (99, 108, 'PERSON'), (150, 162, 'PERSON')]}), ('3.', {'entities': [(0, 1, 'CARDINAL')]}), ('The South by Southwest (SXSW) festival in Austin, Texas, featured an eclectic lineup of emerging artists across various genres, making it a hotspot for music discovery.', {'entities': [(4, 9, 'LOC'), (42, 48, 'GPE'), (50, 55, 'GPE')]}), ("The Berlin Philharmonic, under the direction of conductor Sir Simon Rattle, mesmerized the audience with their flawless interpretation of Mahler's Symphony No.", {'entities': [(0, 23, 'ORG'), (62, 74, 'PERSON'), (138, 144, 'PERSON')]}), ('5.', {'entities': [(0, 1, 'CARDINAL')]}), ('The Country Music Association (CMA) Awards recognized outstanding achievements in country music, with stars like Carrie Underwood and Luke Bryan stealing the show.', {'entities': [(0, 29, 'ORG'), (113, 129, 'PERSON'), (134, 144, 'PERSON')]}), ('The National Association of Music Merchants (NAMM) organized the largest music trade show in the world, providing a platform for manufacturers to showcase their latest instruments and equipment.', {'entities': [(0, 43, 'ORG'), (45, 49, 'ORG')]}), ('The Rock and Roll Hall of Fame, located in Cleveland, Ohio, honors influential musicians and bands that have made significant contributions to the rock genre.', {'entities': [(0, 30, 'ORG'), (43, 52, 'GPE'), (54, 58, 'GPE')]}), ('The American Society of Composers, Authors, and Publishers (ASCAP) protects the rights of music creators by licensing their works and distributing royalties.', {'entities': [(0, 42, 'ORG'), (48, 58, 'ORG'), (60, 65, 'ORG')]}), ('The Montreux Jazz Festival, held annually in Switzerland, attracts jazz enthusiasts and features performances by renowned artists like Herbie Hancock and Chick Corea.', {'entities': [(0, 26, 'ORG'), (33, 41, 'DATE'), (45, 56, 'GPE'), (135, 149, 'PERSON'), (154, 165, 'ORG')]}), ("The National Opera and Ballet Theater of Belarus, situated in Minsk, staged a breathtaking production of Tchaikovsky's Swan Lake, showcasing the talent of their ballet company.", {'entities': [(0, 48, 'ORG'), (62, 67, 'GPE'), (105, 116, 'ORG'), (119, 128, 'LOC')]}), ('The Billboard Music Awards, organized by Billboard magazine, recognized chart-topping artists across various genres, including pop, hip-hop, and R&B.', {'entities': [(0, 26, 'ORG'), (41, 50, 'ORG')]}), ('The Recording Industry Association of America (RIAA) awarded platinum certifications to musicians whose albums reached a million units in sales.', {'entities': [(0, 51, 'ORG'), (121, 128, 'CARDINAL')]}), ('The Electric Daisy Carnival (EDC), one of the largest electronic dance music festivals, transformed Las Vegas into a pulsating hub of music, art, and culture.', {'entities': [(0, 27, 'ORG'), (29, 32, 'ORG'), (35, 38, 'CARDINAL'), (100, 109, 'GPE')]}), ("The London Symphony Orchestra, renowned for its virtuosity and versatility, collaborated with the Royal Ballet to create a spellbinding performance of Prokofiev's Romeo and Juliet.", {'entities': [(0, 29, 'ORG'), (94, 110, 'ORG'), (151, 160, 'PERSON'), (163, 168, 'PERSON'), (173, 179, 'PERSON')]}), ('The National Association of Music Educators (NAfME) promotes music education in schools and provides resources for teachers to nurture young musicians.', {'entities': [(0, 43, 'ORG'), (45, 50, 'ORG')]}), ('The Newport Jazz Festival, held in Rhode Island, is the oldest jazz festival in the United States and has featured iconic artists like Miles Davis and Ella Fitzgerald.', {'entities': [(0, 25, 'ORG'), (35, 47, 'GPE'), (80, 97, 'GPE'), (135, 146, 'PERSON'), (151, 166, 'PERSON')]}), ('The Recording Academy, the organization behind the Grammy Awards, strives to recognize and celebrate excellence in the recording industry worldwide.', {'entities': [(0, 21, 'ORG'), (47, 64, 'WORK_OF_ART')]}), ('The Latin Grammy Awards, presented by the Latin Recording Academy, honor outstanding achievements in Latin music across various genres.', {'entities': [(38, 65, 'ORG'), (101, 106, 'NORP')]}), ('The International Federation of the Phonographic Industry (IFPI) represents the global music industry and works to protect intellectual property rights.', {'entities': [(0, 57, 'ORG')]}), ("The New York Philharmonic, one of the world's most renowned orchestras, performed a sold-out concert at Carnegie Hall, showcasing their mastery of classical repertoire.", {'entities': [(0, 25, 'ORG'), (27, 30, 'CARDINAL'), (104, 117, 'FAC')]}), ('The Essence Festival, held annually in New Orleans, celebrates African-American culture and features performances by influential R&B, hip-hop, and gospel artists.', {'entities': [(0, 20, 'ORG'), (27, 35, 'DATE'), (39, 50, 'GPE'), (63, 79, 'NORP')]}), ('The Juilliard School, renowned for its rigorous music programs, produced many virtuoso musicians who went on to join prestigious orchestras like the New York Philharmonic.', {'entities': [(0, 20, 'ORG'), (145, 170, 'ORG')]}), ('The International Society for Music Education (ISME) organized a conference where educators and researchers discussed innovative teaching methods and pedagogical approaches.', {'entities': [(0, 45, 'ORG'), (47, 51, 'ORG')]}), ('The London College of Music, affiliated with the University of West London, offers a diverse range of music degrees and attracts talented students from around the world.', {'entities': [(0, 27, 'ORG'), (45, 74, 'ORG')]}), ('The American Choral Directors Association (ACDA) hosted a symposium that explored the intersection of technology and choral music, featuring presentations by leading experts in the field.', {'entities': [(0, 41, 'ORG'), (43, 47, 'ORG')]}), ('The Yamaha Corporation, a Japanese multinational, is known for manufacturing high-quality musical instruments, including pianos, guitars, and drums.', {'entities': [(0, 22, 'ORG'), (26, 34, 'NORP')]}), ('The Royal Academy of Music, located in London, has produced numerous internationally acclaimed musicians, including Sir Elton John and Annie Lennox.', {'entities': [(0, 26, 'ORG'), (39, 45, 'GPE'), (120, 130, 'PERSON'), (135, 147, 'PERSON')]}), ('The International Jazz Festival, organized by Jazz at Lincoln Center, showcased performances by legendary artists like Wynton Marsalis and Herbie Hancock.', {'entities': [(0, 31, 'ORG'), (46, 53, 'ORG'), (54, 68, 'FAC'), (119, 134, 'PERSON'), (139, 153, 'PERSON')]}), ('The Berklee College of Music, located in Boston, is renowned for its contemporary music programs and has nurtured talents like Quincy Jones and John Mayer.', {'entities': [(0, 28, 'ORG'), (41, 47, 'GPE'), (127, 139, 'PERSON'), (144, 154, 'PERSON')]}), ('The International Music Council (IMC) is an UNESCO-affiliated organization that promotes music as a tool for social cohesion and cultural exchange.', {'entities': [(0, 31, 'ORG'), (33, 36, 'ORG'), (44, 50, 'ORG')]}), ('The National Association for Music Education (NAfME) advocates for music education in schools and supports music teachers through professional development programs.', {'entities': [(0, 44, 'ORG'), (46, 51, 'ORG')]}), ('The Fender Musical Instruments Corporation, known for its iconic electric guitars, collaborated with renowned musicians to create signature series instruments.', {'entities': [(0, 42, 'ORG')]}), ('The European Broadcasting Union (EBU) organized the Eurovision Song Contest, an annual music competition that brings together participating countries from across Europe.', {'entities': [(0, 31, 'ORG'), (33, 36, 'ORG'), (48, 75, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (162, 168, 'LOC')]}), ('The Australian Chamber Orchestra, known for its dynamic performances and innovative programming, embarked on a world tour to showcase the richness of Australian music.', {'entities': [(0, 32, 'ORG'), (150, 160, 'NORP')]}), ("The Recording Artists' Coalition (RAC) represents the rights and interests of recording artists, advocating for fair compensation and artist-friendly legislation.", {'entities': [(0, 32, 'ORG'), (34, 37, 'ORG')]}), ('The London International Festival of Early Music, hosted by the National Early Music Association, celebrated the beauty and complexity of Renaissance and Baroque music.', {'entities': [(0, 48, 'ORG'), (60, 96, 'ORG'), (138, 149, 'ORG')]}), ('The American Society of Music Arrangers and Composers (ASMAC) honored legendary film composer John Williams with a Lifetime Achievement Award for his contributions to the industry.', {'entities': [(0, 60, 'ORG'), (94, 107, 'PERSON'), (115, 141, 'WORK_OF_ART')]}), ('The International Bluegrass Music Association (IBMA) recognized exceptional artists and musicians who preserve and promote the tradition of bluegrass music.', {'entities': [(0, 45, 'ORG')]}), ('The Detroit Symphony Orchestra, under the leadership of conductor Leonard Slatkin, performed a groundbreaking multimedia concert that merged classical music with digital art.', {'entities': [(0, 30, 'ORG'), (66, 81, 'PERSON')]}), ('The International Guitar Festival, held annually in Cordoba, Spain, attracted guitarists from around the globe to participate in masterclasses and competitions.', {'entities': [(0, 33, 'ORG'), (40, 48, 'DATE'), (52, 59, 'GPE'), (61, 66, 'GPE')]}), ('The Music Teachers National Association (MTNA) organized a conference that explored innovative approaches to teaching music theory and composition.', {'entities': [(0, 39, 'ORG')]}), ("The Seoul Philharmonic Orchestra, led by maestro Myung-Whun Chung, collaborated with the Korean National Ballet to present a breathtaking performance of Tchaikovsky's Swan Lake.", {'entities': [(0, 32, 'ORG'), (49, 65, 'ORG'), (85, 111, 'ORG'), (153, 164, 'ORG'), (167, 176, 'LOC')]}), ('The International Trumpet Guild (ITG) hosted a symposium where trumpet players and enthusiasts gathered to share their knowledge and passion for the instrument.', {'entities': [(0, 31, 'ORG')]}), ("The Vienna Boys' Choir, one of the world's oldest and most renowned choirs, performed a special concert at the Vatican in honor of Pope Francis.", {'entities': [(0, 22, 'ORG'), (24, 27, 'CARDINAL'), (111, 118, 'FAC'), (131, 143, 'PERSON')]}), ('The International Association of Schools of Jazz (IASJ) organized an annual meeting where jazz educators and students came together to exchange ideas and perform.', {'entities': [(0, 48, 'ORG'), (50, 54, 'ORG'), (69, 75, 'DATE')]}), ('The International Association for Jazz Education (IAJE) recognized John Coltrane as a groundbreaking saxophonist who revolutionized the genre.', {'entities': [(0, 48, 'ORG'), (67, 80, 'PERSON')]}), ('The Vienna Philharmonic Orchestra, renowned for its rich sound and precision, collaborated with renowned conductor Herbert von Karajan for many iconic performances.', {'entities': [(0, 33, 'ORG'), (115, 134, 'PERSON')]}), ('The Rock and Roll Hall of Fame inducted legendary guitarist Jimi Hendrix for his unparalleled influence on rock music.', {'entities': [(0, 30, 'ORG'), (60, 72, 'PERSON')]}), ('The National Association of Music Merchants (NAMM) organizes the largest music trade show, attracting musicians and industry professionals from around the world.', {'entities': [(0, 43, 'ORG'), (45, 49, 'ORG')]}), ('The Royal Albert Hall, a prestigious concert venue in London, has hosted performances by renowned musicians such as Yo-Yo Ma and Lang Lang.', {'entities': [(54, 60, 'GPE'), (116, 124, 'PERSON'), (129, 138, 'PERSON')]}), ('The International Trombone Festival, organized by the International Trombone Association (ITA), celebrates the versatility and artistry of trombone players.', {'entities': [(0, 35, 'ORG'), (50, 88, 'ORG'), (90, 93, 'ORG')]}), ('The American Society of Composers, Authors, and Publishers (ASCAP) protects the rights of musicians by ensuring they receive fair compensation for their creative works.', {'entities': [(0, 42, 'ORG'), (48, 58, 'ORG'), (60, 65, 'ORG')]}), ('The Montreux Jazz Festival, held annually in Switzerland, has featured iconic performers like Miles Davis and Ella Fitzgerald throughout its rich history.', {'entities': [(0, 26, 'ORG'), (33, 41, 'DATE'), (45, 56, 'GPE'), (94, 105, 'PERSON'), (110, 125, 'PERSON')]}), ('The Metropolitan Opera House in New York City attracts opera lovers with its world-class productions, featuring exceptional vocalists such as Luciano Pavarotti.', {'entities': [(0, 28, 'ORG'), (32, 45, 'GPE'), (142, 159, 'PERSON')]}), ('The American Federation of Musicians (AFM) represents professional musicians and ensures they receive fair wages and working conditions.', {'entities': [(0, 36, 'ORG'), (38, 41, 'ORG')]}), ('The Newport Jazz Festival, one of the oldest jazz festivals in the United States, has showcased the talents of jazz legends like Duke Ellington and Louis Armstrong.', {'entities': [(0, 25, 'ORG'), (27, 30, 'CARDINAL'), (63, 80, 'GPE'), (134, 143, 'PERSON'), (148, 163, 'PERSON')]}), ('The London Symphony Orchestra, under the baton of Sir Simon Rattle, mesmerizes audiences with their interpretations of classical masterpieces.', {'entities': [(0, 29, 'ORG'), (54, 66, 'PERSON')]}), ('The International Bluegrass Music Association (IBMA) honors influential bluegrass musicians, including Bill Monroe and Alison Krauss, for their contributions to the genre.', {'entities': [(0, 45, 'ORG'), (103, 114, 'PERSON'), (119, 132, 'PERSON')]}), ('The National Academy of Recording Arts and Sciences, responsible for the Grammy Awards, recognizes outstanding achievements in the music industry across various genres.', {'entities': [(0, 51, 'ORG'), (69, 86, 'WORK_OF_ART')]}), ('The Berlin Philharmonic, led by conductor Herbert von Karajan, captivates audiences with its precision and commitment to musical excellence.', {'entities': [(0, 23, 'ORG'), (42, 61, 'PERSON')]}), ('The Country Music Association (CMA) Awards celebrates country music icons like Johnny Cash and Dolly Parton for their contributions to the genre.', {'entities': [(0, 29, 'ORG'), (79, 90, 'PERSON'), (95, 107, 'PERSON')]}), ('The International Society for Music Education (ISME) promotes global collaboration and research in music education, supporting teachers and students worldwide.', {'entities': [(0, 45, 'ORG'), (47, 51, 'ORG')]}), ("The Vienna Boys' Choir, known for its ethereal vocals and centuries-old tradition, continues to enchant audiences with its enchanting performances.", {'entities': [(0, 22, 'ORG'), (58, 71, 'DATE')]}), ('The American Choral Directors Association (ACDA) brings together choral music enthusiasts and professionals, promoting excellence in choral singing.', {'entities': [(0, 41, 'ORG'), (43, 47, 'ORG')]}), ('The International Federation of the Phonographic Industry (IFPI) represents the global music industry, advocating for copyright protection and fair compensation for artists.', {'entities': [(0, 57, 'ORG')]}), ('The Royal Opera House in Covent Garden, London, showcases opera productions featuring world-renowned singers like Plácido Domingo and Maria Callas.', {'entities': [(4, 21, 'ORG'), (25, 38, 'GPE'), (40, 46, 'GPE'), (114, 129, 'PERSON'), (134, 146, 'PERSON')]}), ('The National Association for Music Education (NAfME) supports music educators in providing quality music instruction to students of all ages.', {'entities': [(0, 44, 'ORG'), (46, 51, 'ORG')]}), ('The International Trumpet Guild (ITG) promotes trumpet performance and education, organizing conferences and competitions for trumpet players worldwide.', {'entities': [(0, 31, 'ORG')]}), ('The New York Philharmonic, led by conductor Leonard Bernstein, has gained worldwide acclaim for its exceptional musicianship and groundbreaking performances.', {'entities': [(0, 25, 'ORG'), (44, 61, 'PERSON')]}), ('The International Dance Music Awards (IDMA), held annually at the Winter Music Conference, recognizes outstanding achievements in electronic dance music.', {'entities': [(0, 36, 'ORG'), (50, 58, 'DATE'), (62, 89, 'EVENT')]})]